var title = "Conjugue os seguintes verbos. Não inclua a pessoa.";

var questions = [

  {
    prompt: "(eu) moro",
    answer: ["μένω"],
    partial: ["μενω"],
  },

  {
    prompt: "(tu) moras",
    answer: ["μένεις"],
    partial: ["μένεισ"],
  },

  {
    prompt: "(eu) espero",
    answer: ["περιμένω"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "(eu) quero",
    answer: ["θέλω"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "(tu) queres",
    answer: ["θέλεις"],
    partial: ["θέλεισ"],
  },

  {
    prompt: "(eu) faço",
    answer: ["κάνω"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "(tu) fazes",
    answer: ["κάνεις"],
    partial: ["κάνεισ"],
  },

  {
    prompt: "(eu) sei",
    answer: ["ξέρω"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "(tu) sabes",
    answer: ["ξέρεις"],
    partial: ["ξέρεισ"],
  },
  
  {
    prompt: "(eu) tenho",
    answer: ["έχω"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "(tu) tens",
    answer: ["έχεις"],
    partial: ["έχεισ"],
  },

];
  